disruptarian.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy -

### Your privacy is critically important to us.

Disruptarian Radio is located at:

Disruptarian Radio  
PO BOX 2219  
8083656628

It is Disruptarian Radio’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [https://disruptarian.com](https://disruptarian.com/) (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “https://disruptarian.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Disruptarian Radio collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Disruptarian Radio’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Disruptarian Radio’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Disruptarian Radio may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Disruptarian Radio also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://disruptarian.com blog posts. Disruptarian Radio only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Disruptarian Radio’s websites choose to interact with Disruptarian Radio in ways that require Disruptarian Radio to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Disruptarian Radio gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://disruptarian.com to provide a username and email address.

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Advertisements

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Disruptarian Radio and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Links To External Sites

Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Disruptarian Radio discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Disruptarian Radio’s behalf or to provide services available at Disruptarian Radio’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Disruptarian Radio’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Disruptarian Radio will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Disruptarian Radio discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Disruptarian Radio believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Disruptarian Radio, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of https://disruptarian.com and have supplied your email address, Disruptarian Radio may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Disruptarian Radio and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Disruptarian Radio takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Aggregated Statistics

Disruptarian Radio may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Disruptarian Radio may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Disruptarian Radio does not disclose your personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

To enrich and perfect your online experience, Disruptarian Radio uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Disruptarian Radio uses cookies to help Disruptarian Radio identify and track visitors, their usage of https://disruptarian.com, and their website access preferences. Disruptarian Radio visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Disruptarian Radio’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Disruptarian Radio’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Disruptarian Radio’s use of cookies.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Disruptarian Radio may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Disruptarian Radio’s sole discretion. Disruptarian Radio encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Credit & Contact Information

This privacy policy was created at [termsandconditionstemplate.com](https://disruptarian.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/privacy-policy-generator "Privacy policy template generator"). If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via [email](mailto:) or [phone](tel:8083656628).

Hits: 274
